[Music]
[Música]
eh What else What else do we have to do around
eh Qué más Qué más deber tenemos por
here Oh that he has nothing to fear nothing to
aquí Oh que nada teme nada tiene que
hide and it seems that there are those who
esconder y al parecer hay quienes
prefer to keep some things to themselves Oh It
prefieren mantener algunas cosas Oh
seems that Andy Andy reveals okay this is
Parece ser que Andy Andy revela vale es
the channel in case you want to see it in full
el canal por si queréis verlo completo
The live broadcast has dropped a bombshell not on the
El directo ha dado una bomba no sobre el
subject of Well you already know that Ricky
tema de la Bueno ya sabéis que Ricky
is accused in a in a on a subject of
está imputado en un en una en un tema de
alleged gender violence eh And it is I
presunta violencia de género eh Y está
congratulate you Javi for being able to read what
Te felicito Javi por poder leer lo que
gun says passes I don't understand anything It's that the
dice gun pasa Yo no entiendo nada Es que
large text no Karime but out of
el el texto grande no Karime pero por
laziness like As if skipped but
peresa así Como salteado no pero
listen to me eh well this exclusive that
escúchame Eh bueno esta exclusiva que ha
Andy has given practically apparently is that there
dado Andy prácticamente por lo visto es
is news about the procedure
que hay novedades sobre el procedimiento
in which Ricky is accused they are
en el que Ricky está imputado lo están
investigating him for alleged
investigando por presunta violencia de
gender violence because Ali reported him okay You already
género porque Ali lo denunció vale Ya
know that it is a procedure eh that
sabéis que es un procedimiento eh que
is underway and that it has been a while that
está en marcha y que ya hace tiempo que
or rather I don't know if ag will say the date here
o sea no sé si ag dirá por aquí la fecha
but it has been a while and there have already been
pero ya tiene tiempo y ya ha habido
things or rather there have already been already alali had to
cosas o sea ya ha habido ya alali tuvo
go to the court to testify they
que ir al jugado a testificar la
called her and I imagine that  they must have called
llamaron y me imagino que habrán llamado
Ricky or something like that let's let's
a Ricky o algo por el estilo vamos a
listen to it hidden wink puts
vamos a escucharlo escondida guiño pone
this tet 50 to the first person who
este tet 50 a la primera persona que
guesses the exact time that Dani
adivine la hora exacta a la que Dani
knocks down this vi to continue hiding
tumba este vi para seguir ocultando
evidence evidence son what evidence eh your
pruebas pruebas hijo qué prueba eh tu
account has been blocked just like they
cuenta ha sido bloqueada tal cual le
blocked his account like in Normal
bloquearon la cuenta como en Normal
copyright owned Daniel okay it's
copyright owned Daniel vale que se
supposed to be Dallas such and such And that and well
supone que es Dallas tal y Y eso y bueno
this guy talks a lot about
este tío se llena la boca de hablar de
someone else when he shouldn't be
otra persona cuando él no debería de
talking and he says well in the end I'm not saying it I'm
hablar y dice pues al final no lo digo
saying it a judge What things the judge
yo lo dice una jueza Qué cosas la jueza
annuls this guy's contract for I don't know what
anula el contrato de este por no sé qué
thing and such Ricky how bad you're going to
cosa y y tal Ricky qué mal te vas a
play your own tweets I swear man
jugar tus propios tweets te lo juro tío
but besides it's that it doesn't make
pero es que aparte es que no tiene
sense well in the end I'm not saying it I'm
sentido pues al final no lo digo yo lo
saying it a judge as if this had proven
dice una jueza como si esto le hubiera
Ricky right in some of
dado la la razón a Ricky en alguna de
the antics that he said anyway he's
las payasadas que él decía sea es que
playing with little kids dude let's
juega con los niños pequeños tío vamos a
see what Ricky said was that the
ver lo que Ricky decía era que el los
confidentiality contracts of Dallas
contratos de confidencia idad de Dallas
Dallas used them to abuse and
Dallas los utilizaba para abusar y
mistreat people with  that he was
maltratar de las personas con las que se
rolling around and of course they couldn't
enrollaba y que claro no lo podían
report it because that would mean having to
denunciar porque eso significaría tener
tell a lawyer or a judge
que contárselo a un abogado o a un juez
and they are third parties so they would
y son terceras personas entonces
break confidentiality I mean what
romperían la confidencialidad O sea lo
you were saying Ricky is that you're stupid
que tú decías Ricky es que eres tonto
in other words what you were saying is
con otras palabras lo que tú decías es
that you thought you were criticizing
que te creías que estabas criticando a
Dallas but in reality what you
Dallas pero en realidad lo que tú
were saying is that you were stupid So
estabas diciendo es que tú eras tonto
no no I don't understand Well they're going to play against you really they're going to play your own tweets against you I swear I swear we saw this one Ah no we didn't see this one that they're going to play against you starting to criticize
tu estud en contra ponerse a criticar
aas for like the guy just filed a
aas por o sea el tío acaba de poner una
copyright lawsuit for not so that they don't
demanda por copyright por no para que no
give me back the rewind and he has the
me devuelvan el rewind y tiene los
balls to post a tweet saying that
huevos de poner un tweet diciendo que el
Dallas throws away a video for copyright and that's it and he doesn't
Dallas tira vídeo por copyright y ya
give a damn the hypocrite that he
está y le suda la [__] la hipócrita que
is uncle Ricky stop
es efectivamente tío Ricky para para por
stop because the exclusive that I'm
lo sano corta porque la exclusiva que la
going to give already pay attention like
voy a dar ya atentos dle like
subscribe because mm it really is an
suscribiros porque mm de verdad es una
exclusive and It's that I'm going to look at it because I do
exclusiva y Es que voy a mirarlo porque
n't  I know the exact date March 12th
no me sé la fecha exacta el 12 de marzo
Ricky declares telematically on
declara Ricky de forma telemática sobre
the Ali issue I'll leave it there I mean
el tema del Ali ahí lo dejo Ahí lo o sea
Ricky has to declare
Ricky tiene que declarar de forma
telematically I imagine because he has
telemática me imagino que porque lo ha
requested it to not go in person for whatever reason
solicitado para no ir en persona por lo
okay telematically it
que sea vale de forma telemática
means Well that he is going to a court that has
significa Pues que él va a un jugado que
been accepted for this no that it will be
haya sido aceptado para esto no que será
the one in Andorra or the one in Córdoba or the one in Córdoba
el de andorra o el Córdoba o el de
no I don't know the truth or at home he
Córdoba no no sé la verdad o en su casa
can also do it from home
también lo puede hacer desde su casa
okay What's up Fran but That is to
vale Qué pasa Fran pero Eso es para
put it or what is an audio to put it or
ponerlo o qué es un audio para ponerlo o
what marujo So Ricky Eddie they
qué marujo O sea que Ricky Eddie ya ya
are already well it is that he is accused the
lo están bueno es que está imputado el
other day Pablo said the number of the
otro día Pablo dijo el número de
diligence I don't know what I don't know how
diligencia no sé qué no sé cuánto que
much that they were open and and we will see how how the move turns out for him And what is it that And what is it that he is going to declare and is going to excuse himself I don't know I'll leave it on March 12th effectively madam in exactly a month
marzo efectivamente señora en un mes
eh in exactly a month Ricky has to
justo eh en un mes justo Ricky tiene que
declare eh As accused of the issue of
declarar eh Como imputado del tema de la
alleged gender violence and gentlemen
presunta violencia de género y señores
This is the  p exclusive that I obtained And
Esta es la p exclusiva que obtenía Y es
the thing about Ali is that he talks about has
que el tema de Ali va de que habla ha
gone super fast no s let's see super
ido super deprisa no s a ver super
fast it doesn't take time it's going at the
deprisa no lleva tiempo ya va los
times that are and I'm glad that
tiempos que son y me alegro de que la
justice is going fast c no s I don't know
justicia vaya deprisa c no s no sé de
what
qué se caja
Ricky is boxing about it is true how quickly how fast
Ricky es verdad queé rapidez lo rápido
this issue is going I swear he will
que está yendo este tema os lo juro lo
comment on it depending on how busy
comentará por la depende de lo cargado
the
que esté el
court is I prefer not to first than not
juzgado prefiero que no priero que no
Ricky [ __ ] Ricky has already been
Ricky hostias Ricky ya ha sido
notified that by the way He is on
notificado que por cierto Está de
vacation at Disney He has gone to
vacaciones en Disney se ha ido para
Disney with his girlfriend and another girl
Disney con con la novia y otra chica más
So Ricky already has notification of
O sea que Ricky ya tiene notificación de
the issue eh that the other day Wait what he
del tema eh que el otro día Espérate que
is telling me Ah okay I don't know it's that
me está diciendo Ah vale No sé es que
Fran will go like further back in the live and
Fran ira como más atrás en el directo y
and he is commenting on the discussion that
y está comentando sobre la tertulia que
he and I are going to do Okay and and he tells me
vamos a hacer él y yo Vale y y me dice
Listen to it first and you decide your
Escúchalo antes y tú decides tu
responsibility Fran we can call it
responsabilidad Fran le podemos llamar
the discussion without holds barred whoever comes to
la tertulia sin tapujos el que venga a
debate and whoever comes to speak gets
debatir y el que venga a hablar se le
asked the most son of a [ __ ] questions  [ __ ]
hacen las preguntas más hijas de [__]
in the world let's see the idea that we
del mundo a ver la idea que nosotros
have that we're going to be the two of us and we
tenemos que vamos a estar los dos y y
'll obviously have guests and
tendremos invitados evidentemente y
we're counting, commenting on things and
nosotros contando comentando las cosas y
so on, I don't know, we're still
demás no sé todavía estamos estamos
planning How are we going to plan it, what
planeando Cómo la vamos a planear qué
day are we going to put it on and all that stuff,
día la vamos a poner y todo el rollo ese
okay, but yeah, man, of course, let's see, no holds
vale pero sí hombre claro a ver sin
barred, like no, we're not going to monetize
tapujo como que no no vamos a monetizar
a [ __ ] [ __ ], it's clear we already
una [__] [__] está claro ya te
know you Well, we already have the
conocemos Pues eso ya tenemos la
notification, invite says Darío, guests
notifica invit dice Darío invitados
Dalas Dalas and then Dalas No, man,
Dalas Dalas y luego Dalas No hombre
us We can invite a
nosotros Nosotros podemos invitar a
lot of people Ricky is back Ah Well, he's already
mucha gente a Ricky ya ha vuelto Ah Pues
taken it if the subject goes fast
Ya la ya la ha cogido si va rápido el
because there are serious things, no Read me
tema porque hay cosas graves no Léeme
up, I'm going Ana, I'm back, I'm back
arriba voy Ana ya he vuelto ya he vuelto
eh Ana, what did you tell me Pablo, he doesn't
eh Ana qué me dijiste Pablo es no se
dare, he's back, he's opened, he's taken a
atreve ha vuelto ha abuerto ha llevado
flake Look how good Ana, what did you tell me Jo, it
copo Mira que bien Ana qué me dijiste Jo
's that no, I can't find him, damn lauti
es que no no lo encuentro [__] lauti
50 members but this one, what a gift, no
50 miembros pero este qué regalazo no
Hey, but we were here, super chill
Oye pero que estábamos aquí super chill
Look what a gift 16 of 50 super chat 50
Mira qué regalazo 16 de 50 super chat 50
members how are you, family,
miembros qué tal estáis familia
thank you very much and  and above all I want
muchísimas gracias y y sobre todo Quiero
a round of applause in the chat for lauti who has
un aplauso en el chat para lauti que ha
given away 50 members No more, no less, which is no
regalado 50 miembros Ni más ni menos que
small
no es poca
thing let's see if I can find you queen And that we are
cosa a ver si te encuentro reina Y eso
going to have news very very soon
que vamos a tener noticias mu muy pronto
Oh how scary trolls I don't know what
Uy qué miedo [__] no sé qué es
exactly you want me to see Ana I
exactamente lo que quieres que vea Ana
understand that it depends on after
entiendo que depende de la después de
that statement Well, the
esa declaración Pues el
host Rodri just gave away 50 and lauti
[__] Rodri acaba de regalar 50 y lauti
another 50 but this that has been in 2
otro 50 pero esto que han sido en 2
minutes 150 members in 2 minutes Fran I
minutos 150 miembros en 2 minutos Fran O
mean our chat Fran eh it's going to give a
sea la tertulia nuestra Fran eh va a dar
lot to talk about eh it's going to give a lot to
mucho que hablar eh va a dar mucho que
talk about the bad thing is that it's not going to monetize
hablar lo malo es que no va a monetizar
and and and and yes it's going to cost me money in
y y y y si me va a costar dinero en
lawsuits every moment but well
demandas a cada momento pero bueno
listen to me after this after
escúchame después de esto después de
this are the normal preliminary proceedings
esto son las diligencias previas
Okay then it depends on how they
normales Vale entonces depende de como
see the case after Ricky's testimony
vean el caso después de la testifical de
Then a
Ricky Entonces se se abriría
trial procedure would be opened or not okay I
procedimiento a un juicio o no vale que
understand that Ricky's defense will ask for it to
entiendo que la defensa de Ricky pedirá
be archived But well with things
que se archive Pero bueno con las cosas
that are there I don't know if they will succeed or
que hay no sé yo si lo conseguirá o
not  [ __ ] and it's that I have the
no están cagado e es que yo tengo la
morning of the do busy with
mañana del do ocupada en consultas
medical consultations bets are accepted he will answer
médicas se admiten apuestas contestará
Ali's lawyer's questions [ __ ]
las preguntas del abogado del Ali
bets are accepted he
hostias se admiten apuestas
will answer he will answer little things he will tell the
contestará contestará cositas dirá la
truth he will not answer let's see of course he
verdad no contestará a ver claro es que
may not testify he may not not
él puede no declarar él puede no no
answer the questions no I don't know if
contestar a las preguntas no no sé si
from the judge and the prosecutor eh But well if he
del juez y del fiscal eh Pero bueno si
refuses to answer the questions
se niega responder las preguntas Dios
my God Ricky he thinks that the courts are
mío el Ricky él cree que los juzgados le
going to pay for the nonsense he does on
va a valer las tonterías que hace en
YouTube of course the kid applauds him and his
YouTube claro le aplaude el niño y sus
fantasies Ah what a mess man no no eh Ricky has
fantasías Ah qué líos tío no no eh Ricky
already been notified which of all the
ya fue notificado cuál de todas de las
lawsuits he has from Jeje biogen the thing
demandas que tiene de Jeje biogen lo de
with Lali is on the Lali issue So
lo de Lali es en el tema de Lali Así que
nothing gives too much time the subject takes too long
nada da para largo da para largo el tema
I obviously saw it coming that it was going to take too
yo obviamente me lo veía venir que iba a
long because H there are many
dar muy para largo porque H hay muchas
things in fact As I saw you know I was the one
cosas de hecho Como vi sabéis yo fui la
who compiled absolutely all the
que recopiló absolutamente todos los
videos that by the way are no longer on his
vídeos que por cierto ya no están en su
channel I have them all downloaded and he
canal los tengo descargados todos y
deleted videos recently I don't know if when
borró vídeos hace poco no sé si cuando
he got the notification or whatever he
le llegó la notificación o lo que sea
deleted deleted content look here
borró borró contenido mira aquí aparece
a you appears  let's say Ricky has every day, I
un tú ponte que Ricky tiene cada día me
curse my mother who gave birth to me, eh, I mean,
cago en la madre que me parió eh o sea
Ricky has 800,000 views every day, a
Ricky tiene cada día 800,000 visitas un
million, okay, so
millón vale o sea que aquí hay borrado
700,000 have been deleted here, if you're here. This is what
700.000 si tú estás Esto es lo que
appears in negative, that means that it's
aparece en negativo quiere decir que
deleted here. Well, maybe 2
aquí está borrado pues Pues a lo mejor 2
million because it's clear what he had
millones porquees claro lo que tuviera
that day minus what he deleted,
ese día menos lo que ha eliminado se ha
like a couple of million
borrado como un par de millones de
views were deleted from his channel on January 22nd,
visitas de su canal el día 22 de enero
okay, apart from that, the other day I
vale aparte de eso yo yo el otro día me
realized when I made that video about
di cuenta cuando hice el vídeo ese de lo
the lawsuit, I realized that I
de la demanda me di cuenta de de que
looked for the video of our
busqué fui a buscar el vídeo de nuestra
truth and it was uploaded, there was a re-upload, this
verdad y estaba subido en había una
video, there was a re-
resubida el vídeo este había una
upload. Well, as of
resubida Pues a partir de la semana
last week, Ricky has deleted it or he has deleted it
pasada Ricky lo ha tirado o lo ha tirado
or he has contacted the person with whom he
o ha contactado con la persona con que
had re-uploaded it to remove it, but
lo tenía resubido para que lo quite pero
come on, m m I would bet because he
vamos m m Yo apostaría porque la ha
deleted it, okay, so I mean, until a week ago,
tirado vale o sea hasta hace una semana
well, I don't know if a week, 10 days or
bueno no sé si una semana 10 días o lo
whatever, okay, because the days go by for me
que sea vale porque los días se me pasan
blown away I'm a youtuber but until
volados soy youtuber pero hasta hace
recently until a couple of weeks ago
nada hasta hace días un par de semanas
Maybe you you were looking for the video our
Quizás tú tú buscabas el vídeo nuestra
truth and a reupload appeared and also
verdad y aparecía una resubida y además
had a ton of views and he threw it away he
tenía un porrón de visita y lo ha tirado
threw it away he threw it away So I
la ha tirado la ha tirado Entonces yo
think I imagine that if
creo me imagino que cuadrando un poco
everything was squared away then the notification must have arrived
todo pues le habrá llegado la
and he must have said [ __ ] it's
notificación y habrá dicho [__] que es
true I [ __ ] on 10 and and I also have it
verdad Me cago en 10 y y lo tengo
with the transcript of everything
también con con la transcripción de todo
in case it's necessary I don't know why he
por si hace falta es que no sé para qué
deletes anything if it's that it doesn't matter I mean it doesn't
borra nada si es que da igual o sea da
matter that he deletes everything and also from
igual que borre está todo y aparte por
what Andrea said and a lot of
lo que dijo Andrea e mucha parte de de
what is in the complaint are
lo que hay en la denuncia son temas
private issues I mean conversations between
privados o sea de conversaciones entre
them discussions and so on so
ellos discusiones y demás
for anything everything is
entonces para cualquier cosa está todo
presented eh he will answer it's already done
presentado eh contestará es que ya está
already what's the point of deleting if anything he
hecho ya para qué vale borrar si acaso
deletes things that aren't there But hey the
borra cosas que no hayan Pero oye la la
people who are now around Ricky
gente que ahora está alrededor de Ricky
edy feminist Well I'll leave it for another
edy feminista Bueno lo dejo para otro
time I know he
momento me consta contestará Es que la
will answer It's that the most likely that yes seeing this week people condemned him for putting it is true dude And it's that he is going to be very in  against his own tweets uncle
en contra a sus propios tweets tío
Andrea that setan doesn't have anything cool
Andrea ese setan no tiene no Mola nada
you have to go somewhere else because I'm a
te tienes que ir para otro que soy un
bit of a boti boti eh how much they have to
poco boti boti eh cuánto te tienen que
hate you my goodness my goodness eh let's see
odiar madre mía madre mía eh vamos a ver
if there in court he starts testifying
si allí en el juicio se pone a declarar
you up me down to the judge and says you
tú arriba yo abajo al juez y le dice tú
up me down I'm famous I have more
arriba yo abajo yo soy famoso Tengo más
money than you or he says old to the judge he doesn't say old old
dinero que tú o le dice viejo al juez no
you don't understand
le dice viejo viejo tú no entiendes
old let's see in court What
viejo vamos a ver en en los jugados Lo
happens is that you have to learn to speak
que pasa que hay que aprender a hablar
with respect let's see if he laughed
con respeto no a ver si tanto que se río
at me so much for my closeness of Zorro let's see if he
de mí por el clp mío del Zorro a ver si
laughs so much there and Explains why
se ríe tanto allí y Explica lo de porque
he has to explain a few
é tiene que explicar unos cuantos de
things that are worse than Zorro's
cosas que son peores que los del Zorro
there he has to explain Why he started
allí tiene que explicar Por qué se puso
laughing in an Ali podcast saying
a reírse en un podcast del Ali diciendo
that he sucked off I don't know what my goodness my goodness
que se la chupó a no sé qué madre
all for all for
mía madre mía tod por tod por por estar
meddling and for joking around and for and for
metiéndose y por estar vacilando y por y
his ego eh for all for being
por su ego eh to por to por estar
broken but look at you eh How
hubiese rot pero fíjate tú eh Cómo cómo
capricious time eh that  I at the
de caprichoso el tiempo eh que yo en su
time When I made the video with the
momento Cuando hice el vídeo con las
exclusives eh apart from the fact that apart from the fact that
exclusivas eh aparte de que aparte de
I interviewed Tudor apart from the fact that I
que entrevisté a tudor aparte de que
commented that Ali in private was going to
comenté que el Ali en privado iba iba
tell her friends that we had to
diciéndole a las amigas que había que
deceive Ricky one of the things that I
engañar a Ricky una de las cosas que yo
said is that Lali was going to report him that she didn't even
dije es que Lali lo iba a denunciar que
quote that Lali was the profile
ni cotizaba que Lali lo era el perfil
besides no I mean the one who was
además no O sea que la que la iba que la
going to report him okay And the guy
iba que lo iba a denunciar vale Y el tío
wrote me a tweet saying that you
me escribió un tweet diciendo que tú
precisely have disappointed me you could have
precisamente me has decepcionado podrías
asked me and he blocked me there he
haberme preguntado y me bloqueó ahí ahí
blocked me then he unblocked me
me bloqueó luego me quitó el bloqueo
when he got over his anger when no
cuando se le pasó el mosqueo cuando no
but then he unblocked me And now what
pero luego me me desbloqueó Y ahora qué
desire to complicate life we ​​​​have
ganas de complicarse la vida nos queda
some places left we go to Mimí we go to
algo lugares nos vamos a Mimí nos vamos
Mimí and what he has sent me places
a Mimí ya lo que me ha mandado lugares
for for Twitter says Lali idea for your
para para Twitter dice Lali idea para tu
chat with Fran to call him
tertulia con Fran para llamarlo
sparking spark more sauce Lali it's
chispeando chispa más salseando Lali es
time to sleep Uy Lali Lili it's time to
hora de dormir Uy Lali Lili es hora de
sleep It's time to sleep Lili already
dormir Es hora de dormir Lili sea ya
enough I'm going to have grandpa here
bastante voy a tener aquí al abuelo
doing things Boomer  like to add
haciendo cosas Boomer como para ponerle
sparkle to the program and at the beginning
chispeando al al programa y al principio
clarify Hey, you know that sparkle is
aclarar Oye que sepáis que chispeando es
sparks plus sauce I mean, incredible eh
chispas más salseando O sea increíble eh
incredible your contribution, I
increíble tu aportación yo te lo
appreciate the intention in what it says
agradezco la intención en lo que cuenta
but I'm almost going to put a chat
pero casi que le voy a poner tertulia
with Fran Eh well chat with Fran not
con Fran Eh bueno tertulia con Fran no
chat and that's it guys eh what can I tell you
tertulia y punto chicos eh qué te digo
that I'm going to bed that well to bed I
que me voy a la cama que bueno a la cama
don't have to record a video for the
no tengo que grabar un vídeo para el
main one that I'll leave you there okay I don't know
principal que os dejo por ahí vale No sé
if on Twitter You're going to have more gossip
si en Twitter Vais a tener más salseo
okay on Twitter You're going to have more gossip
vale en Twitter Vais a tener más salseo
and it's not only that you're going to have more
y no solamente es que vayáis a tener más
gossip on Twitter but there are videos in
salseo en Twitter sino que hay vídeos en
the main one two videos there are in the
el principal dos vídeos hay en el
main one that you have to see two, the one with
principal que tenéis que ver dos el de
Anabel Pantoja and the one I uploaded today
Anabel Pantoja y el que he subido hoy
with the case of
con el caso de
Mari what was Mari's name What is it that we had
Mari cómo se llamaba Mari Qué es que
never talked about this girl
nunca habíamos hablado de esta chica
Well you can see it on the main channel a
Bueno lo veis en el canal principal un
kiss thanks to everyone for the company
beso gracias a todos por la compañía
Thank you very much for the Super chat
Muchísimas gracias por los Super chat
Thank you very much for all the
Muchísimas gracias por todos los
members of the night and we'll see you on
miembros de la noche y nos vemos en
Twitter  Okay, on Twitter you have SEO in
Twitter vale en Twitter tenéis al seo en
[Music]
[Música]
minutes and
minutos i